Kheel, Theodore W. Arbitration files 6021/003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Handi-bag Co., Inc. Arnold Weinstein, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 157)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Garay co. Inc., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 158)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Dofan Handbag Co. Jerry Tritsis, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 159)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbags Doris Allen, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 160)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbags, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 161)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Caprice Handbags, Inc. Henry Leon, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 162)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 163)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Escort - Mam'selle Bags Inc. Evelyn Dratel, et al., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  Mach 14
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Escort - Mam'selle Bags, Inc. French Screven, et al., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Prestige Handbag Co. Wenceslas Reves, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Susan Gail Handbag, Inc., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Escort-Mam'selle Bags, Inc. Mates Wolf Minglegrun, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Smart Style Fashions, Inc. Irving Singer, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and fine Arts Bags, Co. Inc., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Murray Kruger Moses Ziegler, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  aug 10
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbag Co., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Lori Bags, Inc., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association Rosa Rodriguez, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association Sergio Rojas Pedro Santiago, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Judith Lieber, Inc. Lovella Pollard, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Merit Leather Goods, Inc., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Pretty Bags, Inc. Gertrude Rios, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Lowy and Mund, Inc., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Lowy and Mund, Inc., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Sterling Handbag company, Inc., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbags, Inc. Thad Johnson, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Susan Novelty, Inc. Annette Leitz, Doris Leitz, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Harry Levine Corporation Gene Gonzalez, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Carlin Bros. and Fried, Inc., 1972 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and London Leather Novelty Inc., 1972 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Pegi Paris, Inc., 1972 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Milch Handbags, Inc., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Garay and Co., Inc., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Bagatelle Manufacturing Rubin Abrams, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Bernelle Handbag, Co. Stephen Steinbrecher, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Morris Moskowitz Corp., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Manor Handbags, Inc., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, and Viki Handbag, Inc. Henry goldsmith, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Bell Handbags, Inc., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and G and S Handbags Mfg. Co. Inc. Javier Banientos Alta Gracio Marquez, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Alpine Handbag, Co., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and caprice Handbags, Inc., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and fancy Industries, Inc., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and empress, Inc. Rosa Cruz, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Rivoli Handbag Co. Inc., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Excellent Bag Corp., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Max Roth Leather goods, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  Nov 14
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and empress, Inc. Kassem Eladjale, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Etienne Aigner, Inc. Jesus Osorio, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 46)
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association and Colonial Novelties Inc. Alfonso Encarnacion, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  Sept. 10
- PNWU, New York, and the New York Industrial Council of the National Handbag Association, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 48)
- PNWU, New York and Newberg Leather Products Co., Inc. Louis Lopez, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 49)
- PNWU, New York, and New-Berg Leather Products co., Inc. Olga Maldonado, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 50)
- PNWU, New York, and New-Berg Leather Products co., Inc., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 51)
- PNWU, New York, and New-Berg Leather Products co., Inc., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 52)
- PNWU, New York, and New-Berg Leather Products co., Inc., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 53)
- PNWU, New York, and New-Berg Leather Products co., Inc., 1970 (Box 28, Folder 54)
- PNWU of NY and NY Bag co., Inc. Julio Carrion, et al., 1958 (Box 28, Folder 55)
- PNWU of New York and Paris Queen Bags, Inc., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 56)
- PNWU, NY, and Phillips-Buttrick, Inc., 1954 (Box 28, Folder 57)
- PNWU, NY Local 1 and Pretty Bags Company, Inc., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 58)
- PNWU, NY, Local and Pretty Bags, Co., 1974 (Box 28, Folder 59)
- PNWU, Local 1, AFL-CIO, and Primary Handbag, Inc., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 60)
- PNWU NY, Local 1 and Princess Leather Goods, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 61)
- PNWU NY, Local 1 and Princess Leather Goods, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 62)
- PNWU NY, Local 1 and Princess Leather Goods, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 63)
- PNWU, NY, and Princess Leather Goods, Helen Reed, et al., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 64)
- PNWU, NY, and Reisen Handbag, Inc. Gwendolyn Foster, et al., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 65)
- PNWU, New York, Local 1 and Reliable Paring, Co., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 66)
- PNWU, NY, and Rivoli Handbag co., Aurelio Gonzalez, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 67)
- PNWU, NY, Local 1, and Rivoli Handbag Co., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 68)
- PNWU NY, and Robel Handbags, Inc., 1964 (Box 28, Folder 69)
- PNWU, NY, Local 1, and Rolyn Handbag, Inc. Isaac nodelman, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 70)
- PNWU, NY and Ruth Handbag, Inc. Joe Meyer, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 71)
- PNWU, NY and S and W Handbag Company Bernard Faeth, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 72)
- PNWU, NY and SD Leather Goods Corp. Morris Seckler, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 73)
- PNWU, NY and David Sommer Catherine Pesintzis, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 74)
- PNWU, NY, and Stylemaster Leathercraft corp., 1954 (Box 28, Folder 75)
- PNWU, NY, and Suburbia Handbags, Inc. Julio Arriaga (Box 28, Folder 76)
- PNWU, NY, and Suburban Handbags, Inc., 1978 (Box 28, Folder 77)
- PNWU, NY Local 1, and Supreme Leather Prod. Co., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 78)
- PNWU, NY, and Susie Rae Handbag, Inc., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 79)
- PNWU NY, Local 1 and T Lisker Co., Inc., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 80)
- PNWU, NY and Terry Leather goods, Inc. Corbelo Melino, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 81)
- PNWU, NY, and Tropic Handbags, Inc., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 82)
- PNWU, NY, and Venus Handbags, Inc. Eugenio Ricardi, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 83)
- PNWU, NY, and Ziff Bros. Handbag Co. Norman Bell, et al., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 84)
- PNWU, and Adam Steven Leather Goods and Adam Artistic Accessories, Ltd., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 85)
- PNWU, NY, and Friedman Bros. Inc. and Barad and Danzinger Inc. and Division Walter Cohn co. Ltd., 1971 (Box 28, Folder 86)
- Radio and Television Directors Guild, AFL, and Bremer Broadcasting corp. (Television Station WATV), 1955 (Box 28, Folder 87)
- ABC Vending Corporation and Retail Clerks Int'l Association, AFL Jerome Fisher, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 88)
- Furniture Employers Group, and Retail clerks Int'l Ass., et al., 1952 (Box 28, Folder 89)
- Food Fair stores corp. and Local 1500, Retail Food and Grocery Clerks Union, AFL, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 90)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY and Consolidated Ventilating and Duct co., 1965 (Box 28, Folder 91)
- Local Union No. 28 of Sheet Metal workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and Sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical Contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 92)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical Contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1962 (Box 28, Folder 93)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical Contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1962 (Box 28, Folder 94)
  June 14
- Local Union No. 28 of Sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 95)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and Sheet Metal contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical Contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 96)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of greater NY, and Sheet Metal contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1964 (Box 28, Folder 97)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal workers Int'l Ass. Of greater NY, and Sheet Metal contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc. and Mechanical Contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1964 (Box 28, Folder 98)
- Local No 28 of Sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical Contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1965 (Box 28, Folder 99)
- Local Union No. 28 of Sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and Sheet Metal contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc. and Mechanical contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1965 (Box 28, Folder 100)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater NY, and Sheet Metals Contractors Ass. Of NYC Inc. and Mechanical contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 101)
- Local Union No. 28 of Sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater, NY, and sheet Metal contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 102)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l Ass. Of Greater, NY, and sheet Metal contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical Contractors Ass. Of NY, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 103)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical contractors ass. Of NY, Inc., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 104)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical contractors ass. Of NY, Inc., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 105)
  Sept. 25
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical contractors ass. Of NY, Inc., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 106)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical contractors ass. Of NY, Inc., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 107)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical contractors ass. Of NY, Inc., 1969 (Box 28, Folder 108)
- Local Union No. 28 of sheet Metal Workers Int'l ass. Of Greater NY, and sheet Metal Contractors Ass. Of NYC, Inc., and Mechanical contractors ass. Of NY, Inc. Benjamin Rosenthal, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 109)
- American Finishing company and Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 110)
- Local 876, Textile Workers Union of America, and Double Woven Corp. of America Authority John Montalbano, et al., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 111)
- Double Woven corp. of America and Picardy Mills, Inc. and Local 876, Textile workers Union of America, cid, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 112)
- Tile Layers Helpers Union, Local 88, and Various Unions, and greater, NY Tile Contractors Assn., 1954 (Box 28, Folder 113)
- Tile Layers Helpers Union, Local 88, and various Union, and Greater NY Tile Contractors Ass., 1954 (Box 28, Folder 114)
- Tile Layers Helpers Union, Local 88, Int'l Ass. Of Marble, Store and slate Polishers, Rubbers, and Sawyers, Tile and Marble Setters Helpers and Terrazzo Workers Helpers, and Greater NY Tile contractors Ass. Of the Tile & Mantel Contractors Ass. Of A, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 115)
- Union of Telephone workers and NY Telephone company Margaret Gallagher, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 116)
- United Auto workers, AFL-CIO, Local 191, and GE Comp, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 117)
- Int'l Union, United Auto; Aircraft, Ag. Implement Workers of America and its Local 365, and Intertype company, a division Harris, Intertype Corp., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 118)
- united Auto, Aircraft, and Ag. Implement Workers of America (UAW) Local 770, and Intertype corp., 1958 (Box 28, Folder 119)
- Int'l Union, United Auto. Aircraft and Ag. Implement Workers of America, Local 770, and Intertype company, A Division of Harris, Intertype corp., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 120)
- Int'l Union, United Auto., Aircraft and Ag. Implement workers of America, and its Amalgamated Local 770, and Intertype company, a Division of Harris-Intertype Corp., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 121)
- Int'l Union, United Auto., Aircraft and Ag. Implement workers of America, and its Amalgamated Local 770, and Intertype company, a Division of Harris-Intertype Corp., 1960 (Box 28, Folder 122)
- Murray Manufacturing corp. and Local 770 United Automobile Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 123)
- Murray Manufacturing Corp. and Local 770 United Automobile Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 124)
- Murray Manufacturing Corp. and Local 770 United Automobile Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 125)
- Parker-Kalon Division of Gen. American Transportation Corp. and Int'l Union, United Ag. Implemented Workers of Amer (UAW AFL-CIO), Local 778, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 126)
- Parker Kalon Division of Gen American Transportation corp., and Int'l Union United Auto, Aircraft and Ag. Implement Workers of America, Local 770, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 127)
- Int'l Union United Auto, Aircraft and Ag. Implement Workers of America Local 1010, and Lycoming Division - Avco Manufacturing corp., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 128)
- local 1010, UAW, AFL-CIO, and Lycoming Division, Avco Manufacturing Crop., 1958 (Box 28, Folder 129)
- tri-county Brick Corporation and United Brick and Clay Workers of America, Local 981, AFL, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 130)
- RH Macy and United Dept. Stores of America, Local 1-S, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 131)
- Baker & Taylor company, and Book and Magazine Guild, Local #18, United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 132)
- United Petroleum workers and tidewater Ass. Oil comp. Joe Cavanagh, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 133)
  Aug. 29
- Goodyear Tire and Rubber Comp., Inc. and Local 449, United Rubber Cork, Linoleum, and plastic workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 134)
  July 17
- Goodyear Tire and Rubber co., Inc. and Local 449, United Rubber, cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 135)
- Goodyear Tire and Rubber co., Inc. and Local 449, United Rubber, cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 136)
- United Rubber, cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Local 457, and Kentile, Inc., 1955 (Box 28, Folder 137)
- Local 457, United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, and Kentile, Inc., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 138)
- United Steel Workers of America Local 3274, and Crompton and Knowles corp. Worcester Division Joe Lynch, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 139)
- United Steelworkers of America, Local 3274, and Crompton and Knowles Crop., Worcester Division, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 140)
- Continental Can comp. and United Steelworkers of America, Local 4334 Harry Peck, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 141)
- United Teacher of Northport and Rubert Mondannaro, and Northport, E. Northport Board of Education, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 142)
  Nov
- American Brass Company, and Waterbury Brassworkers' Union, Local 1251 Patsy Flammia, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 143)
- the Mattatuck Manufacturing co. and Waterbury Brass Workers Union, Local No. 1251 A Whittaker, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 144)
- the Mattatuck Manufacturing Co. and Waterbury Brass Workers Union, Local no. 1251 UAW Afl-CIO (Box 28, Folder 145)
- Youngstown Education Ass. And Board of Education of Youngstown City School district, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 146)
- Sergeants Benevolent Ass., Lieutenants Benevolent Ass. And Detectives Endowment Ass. Of NYPD and City of New York, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen, and Helper of America Local 445 and food Packers, Canney and Miscellaneous Workers Union Local 220, affiliated with the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and butchers Workmen of North America and BFG, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen, and Helper of America Local 445 and food Packers, Canney and Miscellaneous Workers Union Local 220, affiliated with the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and butchers Workmen of North America and BFG, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  Oct 18
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen, and Helper of America Local 445 and food Packers, Caney and Miscellaneous Workers Union Local 220, affiliated with the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and butchers Workmen of North America and BFG, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen, and Helper of America Local 445 and food Packers, Canney and Miscellaneous Workers Union Local 220, affiliated with the Amalgamated Meat Cutters and butchers Workmen of North America and BFG, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Nassau community college Federation of Teachers Local 3150 and Nassau community college Adjunct Faculty Association, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  Aug
- Newark Teachers Association and Newark Teachers Union, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- John Stevenson and Capitol Records, Inc., 1963 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Real Estate Arb. Roberto Haggiag and Steven Green and Downing St., Ltd., 1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Eckmar Corp. and Murray Malinski, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  March 9
- sports Arbitration Board Report, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Master File of Awards (Other Than Transit, Maritime and Printing Industry), 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  Feb 1966 - Dec 1970
- Misc. Correspondences (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 1)
- TWU, NYCTA, MABSTOA Health Benefits Trust, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- TWU Local 100 and New York city Transit authority, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- TWU Local 100 and surface Transit corp. and transport Workers Union of America Health, Welfare, and Death Benefit Trust, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- TWU Local 252 and MBSA, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  Sept
- Sports Arbitration Files (Box 31, Folder 5)